here are the stories were covering this
여기 이야기가 이걸 덮고 있었다.
week in the category 5 TV newsrooms a
주 5 카테고리의 TV 뉴스 룸 a
tiny drone bill to pollinate flowers has
꽃에 수분을주는 작은 무인 항공기 법안이 있습니다.
been built in Japan a college network
일본의 대학 네트워크에 지어졌습니다.
has been attacked with its own insecure
자신의 안전하지 않은 상태로 공격 당했다.
I OT devices a new implant method could
새로운 임플란트 방법으로는 장치를 사용할 수 없음
give amputees direct nerve control of
절단 된 환자에게 직접 신경 조절을시킨다.
artificial limbs have a vizio tv spying
인공 지능은 TV를 첩보하고있다.
on you and a passenger carrying drone is
무인 항공기를 들고있는 승객은
ready to fly in dubai these stories are
두바이 에서 비행 준비가되어 있습니다.
coming right up don't go anywhere now
지금 당장 오지 마라.
here's another great way you can support
여기 당신이 지원할 수있는 또 다른 좋은 방법이 있습니다.
the shows you love for the category 5 TV
카테고리 5 TV에서 좋아하는 프로그램
network by shopping at gear back that's
장비 를 쇼핑 하면서 네트워크를
right Jeff cap 5 TV / gearbest it's an
제프 모자 5 TV / gearbest 맞아.
online store for the geek streak in him
그를 괴롭히는 온라인 스토어
or the loved ones well of course I mean
또는 사랑하는 사람이 잘 물론 내 말은
especially your loved ones right because
특히 사랑하는 사람들은
cat5 TV / gearbest quite frankly has all
cat5 TV / gearbest는 솔직하게 모든 것을 갖추고 있습니다.
of the greatest tech gifts that you
당신이 가장 위대한 기술 선물의
could ever hope for at rock bottom
절벽에서 절실히 희망 할 수있다.
prices to that cell phone you bet you
너가 너를 내기 한 그 셀룰라 전화에 가격
cap 5gb slash gear vest has a wide
모자 5gb 슬래시 기어 조끼는 넓은 있습니다
assortment of unlocked android cell
잠금 해제 된 안드로이드 셀의 구색
phones and tablets global compute
휴대 전화 및 태블릿 전역 컴퓨팅
consumer electronics those like a great
소비자 가전 제품은 위대한 것을 좋아한다.
gift absolutely from high-tech watches
선물은 절대적으로 하이테크 시계에서
to action cameras headphones even
액션 카메라 헤드셋
virtual reality headsets cat5 TV /
가상 현실 헤드셋 cat5 TV /
gearbest have you covered they literally
gearbest 당신이 말 그대로 그들이 덮여있다.
have it all Jeff literally really it's
제프가 말 그대로 진짜로 가지고있어.
like a super store right from the
슈퍼 저장소 처럼
comfort of your own share at your
너의 자신의 몫의 편안함
computer through the interweb
인터 웹을 통해 컴퓨터
yeah there's no way they have it all
네, 그걸 다 가질 방법이 없어요.
true it's just a bunch of random
사실 그건 그냥 무작위의 무리 야.
electronic except me what about clothes
전자 옷을 제외하고는 전자 메일
yep both men and women fashionable
두 남자와 여자 유행
apparel at rock bottom SuperDuper prices
락 밑의 의복 SuperDuper 가격
kinda like this well look at this coat
이 코트 좀 잘 봐.
what do you think it's a slimming mock
너는 슬리밍 모의이라고 생각하니?
leather jacket I love it it's available
가죽 자켓
for less than thirty dollars plus free
30 달러 이하와 무료로
shipping a camp five dot TV / gear best
캠프 5 도트 TV / 기어 베스트 배송
yeah all right you kinda got me there
그래, 너 괜찮아.
Wow any other questions for me
나에 대한 다른 질문들 와우
definitely now that the winter is past
겨울이 지나간 지금은 분명히
flying season do they have any good
비행 시즌에는 좋은 것이있다.
deals on say to encompass old mine
말에 거래 된 광산을 포함하는
goodness well check this out dude they
세상에, 잘 됐네.
have everything check out over 500
500 개가 넘는 모든 것을 체크 아웃하십시오.
various groans and not only that they're
다양한 신음 소리뿐 아니라
available marked down by about thirty
약 30 개까지 표시 가능
two up to sixty-three percent off the
2 퍼센트에서 63 퍼센트까지
regular price love it what's website
일반 가격은 웹 사이트를 좋아합니다.
again while you're going to find
다시 찾을 때까지.
gearbest on our partners pages for any
우리 파트너 페이지의 gearbest
of your favorite category five TV shows
좋아하는 카테고리 5 개의 TV 프로그램
like new every day category five
새로운 카테고리 5 와 같은 카테고리
technology TV the pixel shadow but of
기술 TV 픽셀 ​​그림자하지만
course if you want to shop absolutely
물론 쇼핑을 원한다면
right now and you want to go straight to
지금 당장 에 가고 싶다.
the site all you have to do is visit
당신이해야 할 일은 방문입니다.
cat5 TV / gearbest that's easy catch
cat5 쉽게 잡는 TV / gearbest
five dot TV / your back that's right
5 도트 TV / 네가 맞아.
happy shopping
행복한 쇼핑
alright I'm Sasha tomatoes in here the
확실히 나는 여기에서 사샤 토마토 해요
top stories for the week of februari 20
februari 20 주간 주요 기사
seconds 2017 an engineer in Japan has
2017 년 일본 의 엔지니어 가
built a 1.6 inch pollinator bought and
구입 한 1.6 인치 수분 조절기를 만들었고
successfully tested it in his labs the
그의 실험실 에서 성공적으로 테스트했습니다 .
drones creator has armed it with paint
드로잉 제작자가 페인트로 무장 한 상태입니다.
brush hairs that are covered in a
머리카락이 덮여있는 브러쉬 털
special gel sticky enough to pick pollen
꽃가루를 줍기에 충분한 끈적 거림
up but not so sticky that it holds on to
그다지 끈적 거리지는 않지만
the pollen when it brushes against
꽃가루가 닦일 때
something else they write that his
그들이 쓰는 다른 것
experiments with the tiny drone show
작은 무인 항공기 쇼 실험
that the drone can indeed carry pollen
무인 항공기 가 실제로 꽃가루를 나를 수 있다고
from flower to flower in the way an
방식 꽃에 꽃에서
insect would though he has yet to
곤충은 아직 가지 않았지만
confirm that seeds results from this
씨앗이 이것으로 인한 결과인지 확인하십시오.
pollination well flown by a human pilot
인간 조종사가 잘 수분을 주었다.
he next hopes to equip the drones with
그는 다음에 무인 비행기를
their own flower recognizing technology
그들 자신의 꽃 인식 기술
for experts discuss the drones asking
전문가들은 무인 항공기에 대해 묻습니다.
could a fleet of robo pollinators
로보 수분 자의 함대가 될 수있다.
replace or at least supplement bees one
적어도 꿀벌 하나를 대체하거나 보충하십시오.
said there is no substitute substitute
대체 대용품이 없다고 말했다.
for bees another pointed out that even
다른 꿀벌들도
if robo bees are developed some flowers
로보 꿀벌은 꽃을 개발하는 경우
will prove harder to pollinate than
수분하기가 더 어려울 것입니다.
others a third expert thought the
다른 사람들은 제 3의 전문가가
technology could scale though it would
기술은 확장 될 수 있지만
need to be mass-produced and the
대량 생산이 필요 하고
engineers we need to develop a reusable
우리는 재사용을 개발할 필요가있다.
pollen collecting gel but a fourth
꽃가루 젤 수집하지만 네 번째
expert remained worried that it just
전문가는 단지 그것이
comes skills are becoming too expensive
오는 기술이 너무 비싸지고있다.
I'm not sure that's going to be cheap
나는 싼 될 것 확실하지 않다
enough not to make blueberries hundreds
수백 마리의 블루 베리를 만들지 않을만큼 충분하다.
of dollars a pint he says three of those
달러의 1 파인트 그가 그 중의 3 명 을 말한다
experts also agreed that the best
전문가들은 또한
solution is just wild bees because
솔루션은 야생 꿀벌이기 때문에
domesticated or not all they have to do
길 들여진 또는이해야 할 모든
is make sure to set aside enough land
토지를 충분히 버려야한다.
conductive to the bees habitat kumari I
꿀벌의 서식지 쿠마리의 I에 도전
agreed that you agree I the bees just
너는 내가 벌들에 동의한다는 것에 동의 했다.
need a home this sounds like sounds like
이 소리 같은 집 소리가 들리네.
Jeff being missing the point entirely
Jeff는 그 요점을 완전히 놓치고있다.
the coolness of a pollinating drunk okay
괜찮아 수분을하기의 술의 차가움
so here's the problem and this could be
그래서 여기에 문제가 있습니다.
a Jeff mindset of mine but I did watch
제프 제 생각 이었지만 제 시계는 보았습니다.
black mirror and I know it talked about
검은 거울과 내가 그것에 대해 이야기하는 것을 안다.
this in the past that this TV shows that
과거에는이 TV가
faded look terrible so it's probably
아마 너무 어둡게 보였다.
terrible yeah okay so let you watch the
끔찍한 그래, 그럼 네가 보자.
show seriously in the episode they come
그들이 온 에피소드에 진지하게 보여라.
up with tiny little robots literally a
말 그대로 작은 로봇으로
and then they the bees start
그리고 나서 그들은 벌들이 시작합니다.
assassinating people and I can't quite
사람들을 암살하고 나는 꽤 할 수 없다 .
make the connection as to why but it's
왜 그런지 연결을해라.
people who aren't liked very much I
별로 좋아하지 않는 사람들.
think that's where there's on with it
그곳에있는 곳 이라고 생각해.
but ok so these bees can recognize
하지만이 꿀벌들이 알아볼 수 있도록
flowers and they pollinate flowers and
꽃과 그들은 꽃과
they no longer need human direction to
그들은 인간의 방향을 더 이상 필요로하지 않는다.
do it so they they form their own forms
그들은 그것들을 만들어서 자기 양식을 만든다.
and colonies and they start pollinating
식민지와 그들은 수분을 시작한다.
like crazy and everybody's happy about
미친 듯이. 모두들 행복해.
it but then people start dying from the
하지만 사람들은 그로부터 죽기 시작합니다.
bees because of fiction you're making
너가 만드는 허구 때문에 꿀벌들.
this up from a TV show I know I'm making
이걸 내가 TV 쇼에서 만들었 어.
it up from a TV show but it just seems
그것은 최대 TV 쇼에서하지만 그것은 단지 보인다
like okay it seems scary other side of
좋아요, 무서운 것 같아요.
the coin okay let's plant a garden on
동전은 괜찮아. 정원은 심어.
Mars okay okay let's take a whole like
화성 괜찮아. 좋아. 좋아.
box load of pollinating robots drone
로봇 수분 무인 로봇
that are autonomous that will land
착륙 할 자치권
themselves in a charging Bay and then
충전 베이 에있는 사람들 과
get up and fly out and pollinate a game
일어나 일어나서 날아가서 게임에 수분을 주다.
so send that out in advance of humans
그래서 인간보다 앞서 보내라.
being sent out so that there's oxygen so
산소가 넘치도록 보내지.
there's oxygen so that there's fruit so
산소가있어 과일이 나옵니다.
that all of these things that that would
그 모든 것들이
have had to have been transported on
에 수송 되다니.
this ship are now they are growing in
이 배는 이제 그들이 자라고 있다.
some kind of a hydroponics right so
수경법에 관한 일종의 권리
we've got pollination have problem ation
우리는 수분을 가지고있어 문제가있다.
of the bees not a place yet oh yeah no
꿀벌의 장소 아직 오, 그래, 아니
as far no as far as I'm concerned as
내가 아는 한 멀리까지
soon as humanity says though we don't
우리가하지는 않지만 인류가 말하는대로 곧
need these anymore then there's a big
이젠 더 이상 필요하다.
problem no I don't think that's where
문제 아니, 그게 어디 라고 생각하지 않아 .
they're going oh it's a supplemental
그들은 오호 그것 보충이야.
thing or I think it would really work
물건이나 나는 그것이 정말로 움직이게 될 것이라고 생각한다.
well in that kind of an environment
그런 종류의 환경에서 잘
where they don't need to have air to get
도착할 공기가 필요없는 곳
started on pollinating and stuff like
수분과 물건에 시작했다.
that I guess okay all right so you
내 생각에 너 괜찮아.
should do maybe your own happy robobee
어쩌면 너 자신의 행복 robobee를해야만한다.
show and my own happy robobee show
쇼와 내 자신의 행복 robobee 쇼
trouble-dee show will call it robobee by
트러블 쇼는 로보 비 라고 부를 거야.
Robbie okay I i do encourage you though
로비 괜찮아. 너를 격려해.
to watch that episode of black mirror
검은 거울의 그 에피소드를 보는
just you see where I'm coming soon
내가 곧 어디로 갈지 알 겠어.
alright feel like we've already seen it
우리가 이미 본 것처럼 느낀다.
here today
오늘 여기에
an attacker compromised over 5000 IOT
5000 IOT 이상으로 침입자가 침입했다.
devices on a campus network including
캠퍼스 네트워크의 기기
vending machines and light sensors and
자동 판매기 및 광 센서 및
then use them to attack that same
그 같은 공격을 사용
network ZDNet confirms in this instance
네트워크 ZDNet 은이 인스턴스 에서 확인 합니다.
all of the DNS requests were attempting
모든 DNS 요청이 시도 중입니다.
to look up seafood restaurants though
해산물 레스토랑을 들여다보기
the attack was eventually blocked by
결국 공격은
cyber security professionals verizon
사이버 보안 전문가 verizon
verizon's managing principal of
버라이존의
investigative response blames the
조사 응답은
problem on device is configured using
장치의 문제는 다음을 사용하여 구성됩니다.
default credentials and says it's only
자격 증명을 기본과는 말한다
going to get worse there's going to be
더 나빠질 것입니다 .
so many of these things used by people
사람들 이 사용하는 많은 것들
with very limited understanding of what
매우 제한된 이해 로
they are there's going to be endless
그들은 끝 이 없을거야.
amounts of technology out there with
거기 에 기술의 양
people and people are easily going to be
사람들과 사람들은 쉽게 될 수 있습니다.
able to get access to the article
기사에 대한 액세스를 얻을 수
suggests ensuring that the IOT devices
IOT 장치가
are on a completely different network to
완전히 다른 네트워크에있다.
the rest of the IT estate but it ends by
IT 재산 의 나머지 부분 은
warning that until i OT manufacturers
내가 OT 제조 업체 까지 경고
bother to properly secure their devices
자신의 장치를 안전하게 보호해야한다.
and the organizations which deploy them
및 배포하는 조직
learn to properly manage them ddos
ddos 를 적절하게 관리하는 법을 배우십시오.
attacks by IOT botnets are going to
IOT 봇넷에 의한 공격은
remain a huge threat sure we've talked
우리가 말한 엄청난 위협이 남아있다.
about this before yeah all about
전에 이것에 대해
passwords and protecting it kinda it
암호 및 보호하기
kind of does become a little bit of
조금은 조금씩 달라진다.
review here on the show but yeah I think
쇼에 여기에서 검토하십시오 그러나 그렇습니다 나는 생각한다
you know the thing is is that we get an
당신이있는 것은 우리가 얻을 것을 알고
internet cable modem sent to us by our
우리가 보낸 인터넷 케이블 모뎀
cable provider to give us internet
케이블 제공 업체가 인터넷을 제공합니다.
access we plug it in it works we've got
액세스 우리는 그것을 우리가 가지고 작품에 연결
access to Wi-Fi and so we're happy we
무선 인터넷에 접속하고 그래서 우리는 우리 행복
never think that okay well it has the
그게 괜찮아요.
passwords on it that my internet service
내 인터넷 서비스에 관한 암호
provider pre-configured those passwords
공급자가 해당 암호를 미리 구성했습니다.
are readily available on the Internet
인터넷 에서 쉽게 이용할 수있다.
yeah so as soon as somebody puts
누군가가 두 자마자
together a script that goes out and
함께 외출 하는 스크립트
searches for say printers we talked
우리가 말한 프린터에 대한 검색
about this last week yeah 150,000
지난 주 에 관해서는 예 150,000
printers were compromised because they
프린터가 손상 되었기 때문에
have the default user names and
기본 사용자 이름 및
passwords people connect them to their
사람들이 암호를
network because they want to be able to
네트워크를 원 하기 때문에
print to them wirelessly and now they're
무선으로 인쇄 하고 지금은
compromised yeah so no we've got to set
타협을 했어. 그래서 우리가 설정해야 해.
up strong passwords even on our internal
우리 내부에서도 강력한 암호를 사용하십시오.
devices our internet of things
사물의 우리의 인터넷 장치
it's really hard to get yourself in the
너 자신을 얻는 것이 정말 어렵다 .
mindset that this is actually something
이것이 실제로 무엇인가 라는 사고 방식
you need to do it's a connected device
연결 한 장치가 필요합니다.
you've got to realize it's not it just
당신은 그것이 단지 그것이 아니라는 것을 깨달아야 합니다.
because it's in my house just because
내 집에 있기 때문에
it's sitting in my basement on a shelf
내 지하실 선반에 앉아있어.
doesn't mean that it's not accessible by
에 의해 액세스 할 수 없다는 것을 의미 하지는 않습니다.
the rest of the world exactly my shoes
나머지 세상은 내 신발이야.
right now I'm having a hard time
지금은 힘든 시간을 보내고있어
accessing my own wireless printer so
내 자신의 무선 프린터에 액세스하기
feel like nobody else is going to be
아무도 다른 사람이 될 것 같지 않다 .
able back you think so eh when it starts
다시 할 수있을 것 같아서 시작 할 때 그렇게 생각해.
spewing out robots yield oh yeah yeah a
로봇을 내뿜어 오, 예, 그렇습니다.
group of researchers have developed a
연구자 그룹은
new kind of human machine interface that
새로운 종류 의 인간 기계 인터페이스
detects individual neuron signals for
에 대한 개별 신경 신호를 감지합니다.
youth in controlling artificial limbs
인공 사지 조절 청소년
the group's findings published on
그룹의 조사 결과는
februari sixth in the journal Nature
저널 Nature 에서 여섯 번째 februari
were reached using a virtual prosthetic
가상 보철을 사용하여 도달했습니다.
Roger rather than a physical device but
물리적 장치가 아니라 로저
the authors say that their neural
저자들은 그들의 신경
electric interface could greatly improve
전기 인터페이스가 크게 향상 될 수있다.
on existing prosthetic control methods
기존 보철 제어 방법
and gave six subjects who had lost arms
무기를 잃어버린 여섯 과목을 주었습니다.
intuitive control of multiple degrees of
여러 도의 직관적 인 제어
freedom current prosthetics mostly rely
자유 현재 prosthetics는 주로 의지합니다
on signals from a user's muscles
사용자의 근육 신호
sometimes after reconnecting them to
때로는 다시 연결 한 후
nerves from their missing limbs but
그들의 사지에서 신경
according to the new paper that method
새로운 신문 에 따르면 그 방법
generates relatively in precise data and
비교적 정확한 데이터를 생성하고
the new study researchers still use
이번 연구의 연구자들은 여전히 사용
muscles as a sort of amplifier reading
일종의 증폭기 독서로서의 근육
their signals with implanted electoral
선거 된 선거인들의 신호
biographical sensors but they filtered
전기 센서는 필터링했지만
the noise of the muscle activation
근육 활성화의 소음
giving more direct readings of neuron
뉴런을 더 직접적으로 읽음
signals then they mapped inner signals
신호는 내부 신호를 매핑
that would normally control particular
일반적으로 특정
motions and use them as inputs for the
모션 을 입력으로 사용합니다 .
virtual prosthetic this gave test
가상 보철이 시험을 보냈다.
subjects much more accurate and precise
피험자가 훨씬 정확하고 정확하게
control by one metric they got an
한 통계로 제어
average of ninety-seven percent signal
평균 97 퍼센트의 신호
accuracy comparable between seventy and
칠십과
eighty five percent for dissing methods
해법에 대한 85 %
that's incredible in addition to
그것은 놀라운 것입니다.
enhanced motion accuracy the use of
향상된 모션 정확도 사용
decoded neural information generally
일반적으로 디코딩 된 신경 정보
showed more accurate measurement of the
의보다 정확한 측정을 보여 주었다
fourth of the subjects intended
대상의 네 번째
movements while there is some advance
운동 몇 가지 사전이있는 동안
work on my electric sensors that can
내 전기 센서로 작업 할 수있다.
control prosthetics without being
보지 않고 보철물을 제어하십시오.
surgically implanted this new method
이 새로운 방법을 수술 적으로 이식했다.
could offer benefits that outweigh the
보다 많은 혜택을 제공 할 수 있습니다.
inconveniences
불편
surgery I would agree the next step for
수술 나는 다음 단계에 동의 할 것이다.
the team will be to demonstrate its
팀은
effectiveness with a physical prosthesis
육체 보철물로 인한 효과
I love this now I don't know how many
나는 이것을 얼마나 좋아 하는지 모르겠다.
people know my mother is a soleta my
사람들은 내 어머니가 내 아들을 알지.
baby she was born with like only one
자기야 자기 처럼 태어났다.
Anna like a half arm right if she has
그녀가 가진 다면 절반의 팔을 좋아하는 애나.
her arm up to her out she was born that
그녀의 팔까지 그녀가 태어났다.
way she's not a man not an amputee but
그녀 는 수족이 아닌 남자가 아니지만
i'm thinking i mean as things develop
나는 물건이 개발되면서 나는 의미한다고 생각하고있다.
now I mean I don't know whether or not
지금은 내가 여부를 알 수없는 의미
this is going to work in her case
이 경우에 효과가있을 것입니다.
especially the fact that she is not
특히 그녀가 그렇지 않다는 사실
young oh right I love you but so there's
젊은 아 맞아 ,하지만 너를 사랑해.
some time that needs to develop but can
개발해야 할 때가 있지만
you imagine if you're born with like not
네가 태어난다면 상상하지 마라.
a full limb and you could actually as a
완전한 사지와 당신은 실제로
child and as you grow like develop the
아이를 키우고 성장함에 따라
ability to use those of you garnishing I
내가 너를 차별 대우하는 능력
think the only thing you'd be lacking at
네가 부족한 유일한 일 이라고 생각해.
that point is the sense of feel but okay
그 점은 느낌이 있지만 괜찮아요.
what could they program that in right
그게 바로 프로그램 할 수 있겠 어?
maybe it's just a matter of your brain
어쩌면 그것은 단지 당신의 뇌의 문제 일 것입니다.
recognizing it right so you might be
당신이 그렇게 할 수있을만큼 올바르게 인식하고 있습니다.
able to program in a sense I gotta be
어떤 의미에서 프로그램 할 수 있어요.
artificial though yeah but I think you
인공이지만 그래,하지만 난 너를 생각해.
could do it I think it could have done
그것을 할 수 있었다 나는 그것이 할 수 있었다라고 생각한다.
so i could have figure that out right
그래서 나는 그걸 제대로 이해할 수 있었어.
I'm just impressed with the fact that
나는 그 사실에 감명 받았다.
they can control an armed with
그들은 무장 한 사람들을 통제 할 수있다.
ninety-seven percent accuracy and I'm
97 퍼센트의 정확도와 나는
saying arm but so now in your mother's
팔을 말하지만 지금은 네 엄마의 말에
case what I wonder is because she was
내가 궁금해하는 것은 그녀가
born that way are the nerve endings
그런 식으로 태어난 것은 신경 결말이다.
there that would need to be tapped into
거기에 두드려 져야 할 것입니다.
I would think so there's no Gunnar I
나는 Gunnar I가 없다고 생각할 것이다.
don't know how yeah yeah so there's your
어떻게 그래, 그래, 그래서 네가있어.
must be right it's just a matter of
맞을 것입니다. 그것은 단지 문제 일뿐입니다.
training the brain right if you do it at
네가 그렇게하면 뇌를 바로 훈련하라.
a young enough age yeah I don't know
젊은 나이에 나는 잘 모른다.
what the neural plasticity is later on
신경 가소성은 나중에 무엇인가?
and I don't even know how to say that
그리고 나는 그 말을하는 법조차 모른다.
let alone what it is right but i'm
그것이 옳은 것은 말할 것도없고 나는 그렇다.
thinking like in the future ok so now
미래에 지금처럼 생각하고 있어
I'm on Team B because now I'm thinking
지금 B 팀에 있습니다. 왜냐하면 지금 내가 생각하고 있기 때문입니다.
in the future if you can do things like
미래에 당신과 같은 일을 할 수있는 경우
that then then that robot hand write the
그때 로봇 핸드는
prosthetics it might be able to touch
그것을 만질 수있는 인공 보철
something cold and actually get a
추운 것과 실제로 얻는 것
feedback into it the brain and that's
그것을 두뇌에 피드백하십시오.
colder that's hot but without hurting
추운 날은 뜨겁지 만 상처는 없습니다.
you it's an easy right now they're
당신은 지금 그들이있어 쉽게입니다
talking about the ability to control the
통제 능력에 대해 이야기 하기.
pressure I know so to be able to be able
유능한 사람이 될 수 있기 를 나는 압니다.
to you know to do that you know like we
너도 알다시피 너는 우리처럼
take for granted right that you know
당신이 알고있는 것을 당연한 것으로 여기십시오.
there's a hit
히트가있다.
the punch and there's the soft touch and
펀치와 부드러운 터치가 있고
for somebody who doesn't have or have
없거나 가지고 있지 않은 사람을 위해
lost a limb or did tie shoelaces like
사지를 잃어 버렸거나 신발 끈을 묶었 다.
that takes internship yelling it you
인턴쉽이 너 한테 소리 지른다.
know absolutely absolutely so cool okay
절대적으로 절대적으로 괜찮아. 알았어.
visio one of the world's biggest makers
세계 최대 제조사 중 하나 인 visio
of Smart TVs is paying 2.2 million
의 스마트 TV는 220 만 달러를 지불합니다.
dollars to settle charges that it
그것을 정하는 달러
collected viewing habits from 11 million
1,100 만 건에서 수집 한 시청 습관
devices without the knowledge or consent
지식이나 동의없이 장치
of the people watching them your TV is
TV를 보는 사람들의
watching you according to a complaint
불만 사항 에 따라 당신을 지켜보고있다.
filed Monday by the US Federal Trade
미국 연방 통상부 (FOMC)
Commission Internet connected TVs from
인터넷에 연결된 TV를 위원회 에서
Vizio contained a CR short for automated
Vizio는 자동화 된 CR 단락을 포함했습니다.
content recognition software without
없이 콘텐츠 인식 소프트웨어
asking for permission the ACR code
ACR 코드 허가 요청
captured second-by-second information
캡처 된 초당 정보
about the videos of TVs displayed the
TV 의 비디오에 대해
software collected other personal
소프트웨어가 다른 개인을 수집했습니다.
information and transmitted along with
정보와 함께 전송
viewing data to server is controlled by
서버에 데이터보기는
the manufacturer physios and sold data
제조업체 physios 및 데이터 판매
to unnamed third parties for purposes of
의 목적을 위해 익명의 제삼자에게
audio audience measurement analysis and
오디오 잠재 고객 측정 분석 및
tracking the tracking started in
추적 시작 추적
february2014 on both new tvs and
2 월 2 일에 새로운 TV와
previously sold devices that didn't
이전에 판매 된 기기
originally ship with a CR software
원래 CR 소프트웨어 와 함께 제공됩니다.
installed the software periodically
주기적으로 소프트웨어를 설치했다.
appended IP addresses to the collected
수집 된 IP 주소 추가
data and also made it possible for more
데이터도 더 것이 가능해진다
details personal information including
다음을 포함한 개인 정보
age sex income marital status household
연령별 성별 혼인 상태 가구
size education level home ownership and
크기 교육 수준 주택 소유권 및
home values to be associated this is
이것과 관련된 집값 은
ridiculous the collection occurred under
우스운 수집이 발생했습니다.
a setting that was described as smart
똑똑한 것으로 묘사 된 설정
interactivity feature a smart
스마트 기능 상호 작용
interactivity feature that enables
상호 작용 기능을 통해
program offers and suggestions so it
프로그램 제안 및 제안
sounds kind of benign the menu never
그런 종류의 메뉴는 결코 좋지 않다.
informed users of the feature also
정보를 사용자에게 알리기도한다.
transmitted viewing habits or other
전송 된 시청 습관 또는 기타
personal information in addition
개인 정보
security researchers had previously
보안 연구원들은 이전에
found that the Vizio TVs failed to
Vizio TV가 실패한 것을 발견 했습니다.
properly validate the HTTPS certificates
HTTPS 인증서의 유효성을 올바르게 검사하십시오.
of servers they connected to when
서버를 연결할 때
transmitting viewing habitat ax
보기 서식지 도끼 전송
that made it trivial for anyone who had
그걸로 누구든지 사소한 일 이었어.
the ability to monitor and control the
모니터링하고 제어 할 수있는 능력
internet traffic passing between the TV
TV 사이를 통과하는 인터넷 트래픽
and the vizio servers to impersonate the
vizio 서버가
servers and view or tamper with the
서버를 보거나 변경할 수 있습니다.
transmitted data under the terms of the
의 조건에 따라 전송 된 데이터
settlement vizio will pay 1.5 million
정착 vizio는 1.5 백만을 지불 할 것이다
dollars to the FTC and 700,000 to the
FTC에 달러 와
New Jersey Division of Consumer Affairs
뉴저지 소비자 보호국
the settlement also requires vivio to
그 합의는 또한 vivio에게
delete all data collected before march
행진하기 전에 수집 된 모든 데이터 삭제
first 2016 I don't know that that's
2016 년 처음 나는 그게 뭔지 몰라.
enough of a punishment to be honest i
정직한 처벌 로 충분하다.
don't i don't like that no lie and say
나는 그저 거짓말하고 말하지 않는 것을 좋아하지 않는다.
you're doing it they didn't lie they
너는 그것들을하고있다. 그들은 거짓말하지 않았다.
just didn't tell the truth that is bad
나쁜 진실 을 말하지 않았어.
as samesies that's why would you like
같은 samesies로 왜 당신은 좋겠어?
this really cool feature what do you
이 정말 멋진 기능은 무엇입니까?
would you say for that much interactive
그 많은 대화 형
yeah like yes yeah you won't want that
그래, 네가 좋아하지 않을거야.
you want to go by the way we're doing
당신은 우리가하고있는 방법으로 가고 싶어
all this stuff how to see the worst you
이 모든 것들이 당신을 최악의 상태 로 보는 법
can recommend what I would like because
내가 뭘 원하는지 추천 할 수있어.
you know exactly what I want at least I
내가 뭘 원하는지 정확히 알지.
got called on it Joey yeah holy that is
그것에 부름 받았다 Joey yeah holy that is
ridiculous how can you do that does
말도 당신은이 수행 할 수있는 방법
anyone who's watching this on a vizio tv
vizio tv에서 이것을보고있는 사람
and if so please comment below what
그렇다면 아래에 의견을주십시오.
action you have had to take in order to
액션 당신을 위해 수행해야했다
protect your personal confidential data
개인 기밀 데이터 보호
how does this make you feel they
이게 너를 어떻게 느끼게 해줄거야?
wouldn't even know that there until this
이걸 알기조차 모를거야.
exact yeah that there that I'm sorry to
정확한 예, 거기 에 나는 유감 스럽다.
break it to you your teeth wash is there
치아를 씻으시오. 거기에있다.
a vizio logo right there if you're
니가 있다면 거기에 vizio 로고가있다.
watching us on a video the video is
동영상에서 우리를보고 비디오
watching you watch us we in turn are
우리가 우리를 차례로 보면서 지켜보고있다.
purchasing your personal data yeah I
네 개인 데이터를 구입하는 중이다.
know where you live your household
네가 네가 사는 곳을 알아라.
income ah let me get it all oh that's
소득 아 내가 그것을 얻을 모든 하자 오
the world we live in folks okay this is
세계 우리는 괜찮이는 사람에 살고
something cool about the world we live
우리가 살고있는 세상에 대해 냉담한 것
in awesome I mean cool yeah Dubai is
굉장한 것에서 나는 두려운 예를 의미한다 Dubai is is
about to have a passenger carrying drone
무인 항공기를 들고있는 승객이있다.
regularly buzzing through its skyline of
자사의 스카이 라인을 통해 정기적으로 윙윙 거리며
the futuristic city state the arrival of
미래 도시 국가 도착
the Chinese made me hang 101 84 which
중국인은 101 84를 교수형에 처하게했다.
has already had have had it flying debut
이미 첫선을 보였다.
/ / connick sale shaped skyscraper hotel
/ / connick 판매 모양의 마천루 호텔
comes as the city has partner
도시에는 파트너가있다.
with several cutting-edge technology
여러 최첨단 기술
companies to introduce futuristic
기업이 미래를 소개
transportation including a hyper lip
하이퍼 립을 포함한 운송
Hyperloop Elon Musk's loading pod that
Hyperlop Elon Musk의 로딩 포드
travels at speeds of up to 1,000 220
최대 1,000 220의 속도로 이동합니다.
kilometers an hour the question is
질문은 시간당 킬로미터입니다.
whether he hang 184 passenger drone will
그가 184 명의 무인 항공기 무인기를 걸 었는지 여부.
really take off as a transportation
운송 수단으로 이륙하다.
alternative in this car clog city
이 자동차 방해물 도시의 대안
already home to the world's longest
이미 세계에서 가장 긴 집
driverless metro metro line the head of
무인 지하철 메트로 라인의 머리
dubai's roads and transportation agency
두바이의 도로 및 운송 기관
said and speaking about the drone this
무인 항공기 에 대해 말하고 말하기
is not only a model we have actually
우리가 실제로 가지고있는 모델 일뿐만 아니라
experimented with this vehicle flying
이 차량으로 비행 실험
into by skies that's cool the craft can
공예품으로 멋지게 하늘 로 날아갈 수 있습니다.
carry a passenger weighing up to 220
220 명까지의 승객을 태우다
pounds and a small suitcase or
파운드와 작은 가방 또는
alternatively a suitcase weighing 220
택일 적으로는 220
pounds or some and a small and a small
파운드 또는 일부 및 소형 및 소형
person smokers for two people sitting on
앉아있는 두 사람의 흡연자
each other's laps at 100 not sure that's
서로의 바퀴가 100 번에 있는지 잘 모르겠다.
legal after strapping into its racecar
그것의 racecar로 끈으로 묶은 후에 법적인
style feeds the craft sole passenger
스타일은 공예 단독 승객을 피드
selects a destination on a touch screen
터치 스크린에서 목적지를 선택 한다.
in front of the feet and the drone flies
발 앞에 놓고 무인 항공기가 날아간다.
there autonomously the drone which has a
거기에 무인 항공기가 자율적으로
battery allowing for a half hour flight
배터리로 30 분간 비행 가능
time and a range of up to 50 kilometers
시간과 최대 50 킬로미터 의 범위
will be monitored remotely by a control
컨트롤에 의해 원격으로 모니터링됩니다.
room on the ground it has a top speed of
지상의 방 은 최고 속도를 가지고있다.
160 kilometers an hour but authorities
시간당 160km 이지만 당국
say it will off it will be operated
꺼져서 운영 될 것이라고 말하다.
typically at 100 kilometers an hour the
일반적으로 시간당 100 킬로미터
drone has been examined by the Dubai
무인 항공기가 두바이에서 검사를 받았다.
Civil Aviation Authority who revealed it
그것을 공개 한 민간 항공 당국
was controlled through 4g mobile
4g 모바일을 통해 제어되었습니다.
internet it is poised to begin regular
인터넷은 정규적으로 시작될 태세이다.
operations in July okay so the last part
7 월의 작전 은 마지막 부분이므로
leads me to the question okay 4G mobile
나에게 괜찮은 4G 모바일 질문에 이르게 해준다.
internet so like your phone your phone
인터넷처럼 휴대 전화가 휴대 전화처럼
so okay so sometimes your cellular
그래서 가끔 괜찮아.
network crashes like sometimes there's a
때때로 네트워크 충돌이 발생 합니다.
solar flare I think that's what causes
태양 플레어 그게 원인이라고 생각해.
that I don't know actually the
나는 사실을 모른다.
positioning of the moon
달의 위치
I know I like sometimes sometimes your
나는 때로는 때로는 너를 좋아한다는 것을 안다.
network crashes and if your network
네트워크가 충돌하고 네트워크가
crashes what happens to your solo pod
솔로 포드에 어떤 문제가 발생합니까?
fly in dubai guy okay well uses it why I
두바이 남자 비행 좋아 잘 내가 왜 사용
question becomes and what does it use
질문은 무엇이되고 무엇이 그것을 사용 하는가?
LTE for hey to communicate back with you
안녕하세요, LTE와 연락하기 위해
know with Central Command kind of thing
중앙 명령으로 알 수있는 종류의 것
for the autonomous cloud infrastructure
자율 클라우드 인프라 스트럭처를위한
the powers at the brain quite possibly i
뇌에서의 힘
would expect that it must you know
네가 알아야 한다고 기대할 거야.
that's how it must communicate back to
그것이 다시 의사 소통을해야하는 방법입니다.
Central Command right but the fact is
중부군 사령관 권한은 있지만 사실은
it's going to have a GPS is going to
GPS가 갈 예정입니다.
have autonomous GPS units that
자율 GPS 장치를
communicate with the GPS satellites and
GPS 위성과 통신 하고
at any time if you've ever flown a drone
혹시 라도 무인 항공기에가 본 적이 있다면 언제든지
that has GPS you're going to be
네가 할 GPS가있어.
connected to four or five or more GPS
4 개 또는 5 개 이상의 GPS에 연결
satellites at any given time so if one
주어진 시간에 위성 하나를 그렇다면
goes out of range or loses connection
범위를 벗어나 거나 연결이 끊어짐
you're communicating with others right
너는 다른 사람들과 올바르게 대화하고있다.
same time but quite often I mean if this
같은 시간이지만 꽤 자주 나는 이것이
is anything like and this is going to be
그리고 이런 일이 될 것입니다
this has to be like this is carrying a
이것은 이것이 가지고 다니는 것과 같아야한다.
passenger so it's got to be the best
승객 은 최고가되어야합니다.
autonomous features of drone usage and
무인 항공기 사용 및 자율 기능
I've slowed my drone and I know that if
나는 내 무인기를 늦췄다.
I lose satellite signal it's going to
나는 위성 신호를 잃어 버린다.
just hover there or it's going to
그냥 마우스로 가리 키거나 갈 예정입니다.
reunite a siz it's going to return home
재결합 시키면 집으로 돌아갈거야.
to me or it's going to just there's
나에게 또는 그냥 거기에 갈거야.
there's a couple of different modes but
두 가지 모드가 있지만
if I lose connection with my controller
내 컨트롤러와의 연결이 끊어진 경우
I can either have my drums sit hovering
나는 내 드럼을 유혹에 빠뜨릴 수있다.
automatically or come back home to me oh
자동적으로 또는 나에게 집으로 돌아 간다 오
so it would have features like that so
그래서 그것은 그렇게 특징 을 가질 것입니다.
if LTE lost connection it would say okay
LTE가 연결을 끊으면 괜찮을거야.
I've lost connection either hover here
여기에 마우스를 가져 가면 연결이 끊어졌습니다.
or safely land at a you know maybe they
또는 당신이 아마 알고있는 곳에 안전하게 착륙 할 수 있습니다.
have specific landing sites that are
특정 방문 사이트를 보유하고 있어야합니다.
allowed to land that's true it was a
착륙이 가능하다는 것은 사실이었습니다.
great story until I heard cellular
내가 들었 때까지 위대한 이야기
network and i thought was sometimes my
네트워크와 나는 때로는 내 생각
cell phones a little dodgy I got
휴대폰 좀 피곤해.
thinking about the fact that you know we
우리가 알고 있다는 사실을 생각해 보라.
think about it traveling at 100
100시에 여행하는 것을 생각해보십시오.
kilometers an hour when it can go faster
시간이 더 빨리 갈 수있는 시간당 킬로미터
and you think 100 kilometers an hour
그리고 당신은 100 킬로미터를 1 시간으로 생각합니다.
that's not very fast considering people
사람들을 생각하면 그렇게 빠르지는 않습니다.
do you know here around here 120 on the
너 여기에 120 여기 주위에 알고 있니?
highway is not unheard of sometimes fast
고속도로가 전례가없는 경우도 있습니다.
or not not myself but you see people
또는 나 자신은 아니지만 사람들 을 봅니다.
zubin by me so it doesn't sound very
나에 의해 zubin 그래서 그것은 아주 소리가 나지 않는다.
fast we were traveling like that but
빨리 우리는 그렇게 여행하고 있었다. 그러나
when you're in a clogged congested
막혔을 때 막히다.
city where traffic is stopped yeah yeah
교통이 멈추는 도시 예. 예.
a hundred kilometers an hour is going to
한 시간에 백 킬로미터가 갈거야.
be like paradise for the guy who's got
가지고있는 사람에게 천국처럼되다.
to get to work could you imagine having
당신이 상상할 수있는 일을 얻을 수 있습니다
these buzz around like crazy yeah wait
이 미친 듯이 주위에 버즈가 기다려.
direct like I'm going to work so all of
나는 모든 것을 그렇게 일하게 될 것 같은
a sudden this takes me up like a cab and
갑자기 이것은 택시처럼 나를 데려 간다.
takes me directly to work and lands on
나를 직장과 땅으로 직접 데려 간다.
the roof and I get out and then they're
지붕 과 나는 밖으로 나간다.
right no having to go through the turns
턴을 통과 할 필요가 없다.
and traffic lights and everything this
교통 신호등 이 모든 것을
is not bad this is not bad at all now
나쁘지 않다. 이제는 나쁘지 않다.
there's a whole bunch of people that are
많은 사람들이 있습니다.
like I need to get down to 220 ya doing
나는 220 야드에 이르기 까지 해야 해.
some lunges while they're waiting for
그들이 기다리고있는 동안 약간의 돌진
this to develop puts down the bucket of
이 발전을 위해 양동이를 내려 놓습니다.
chicken free bucket roll I'm sorry sorry
닭고기 버킷 롤 죄송합니다. 죄송합니다.
they will be coming in the extra large
그들은 초대형에 올 것 입니다.
model matter thanks for watching the
모델 문제를 주셔서 감사 합니다.
category 5 TV news room don't forget to
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 룸 잊지 마세요
Like and subscribe for all your tech
모든 기술을 좋아 하고 구독하십시오.
news with a slight Linux bias and for
약간의 리눅스 바이어스 가있는 뉴스
more free content be sure to check out
더 많은 무료 콘텐츠를 확인하십시오
our website from the category 5 TV news
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 에서 우리의 웹 사이트
room I'm Sasha tomatoes
나는 사샤 토마토 야.
[Music]
[음악]
you
당신